JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 8
YUKAKO YAMAGISHI
FALLS IN LOVE, PART 1
CHEMISTRY LAB
CHARM
REVERB
KOICHI HIROSE
YEAR 1
ENGLISH EXAM ANSWER SHEET
QUIZ 2 KOICHI HIROSE
KOICHI HIROSE
JUBILANT MUSIC
PRIMORDIAL MUSIC
ILLUSIONARY MUSIC
JUBILANT MUSIC
TAISHO
EPISODE 9
YUKAKO YAMAGISHI
FALLS IN LOVE, PART 2